1,000,000 tons. 100,000 lives. 100 minutes.
Unstoppable is a action, thriller film directed by Tony Scott.
When a massive, unmanned locomotive roars out of control, the
threat is more ominous than just a derailment.
The train is laden with toxic chemicals, and an accident would
decimate human life and cause an environmental disaster.
The only hope of bringing the train to a safe stop is in the hands of veteran engineer Frank Barnes, and
young conductor Will Colson, who must risk their lives to save those in the runaway's path.
Inspired by true events.
Frank Barnes, played by Denzel Washington.
Will Colson, played by Chris Pine.
Connie Hooper, played by Rosario Dawson.
Oscar Galvin, VP of Operations, played by Kevin Dunn.
Inspector Scott Werner, played by Kevin Corrigan.
Ned Oldham, played by Lew Temple.
Unstoppable is a 2010 American disaster thriller film directed and produced by Tony Scott,
written by Mark Bomback, and starring Denzel Washington and Chris Pine.
It is based on the real-life CSX 8888 incident, telling the story of a
runaway freight train and the two men who attempt to stop it.
It was the last film Scott directed before his death in 2012.
The film was released in the United States on
November 12, 2010, by 20th Century Fox.
It received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed $167.8
million against a production budget between $85–100 million.
It was nominated for an Oscar for Best Sound Editing at the 83rd Academy Awards, and for Best Action
Movie at the 2011 Critics' Choice Movie Awards, but lost to Inception in both cases.
The film explores themes of pennsylvania, usa, locomotive,
freight train, evacuation, based on true story.
The tone is intense.